<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kshisen.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KShisen</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KShisen</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KShisen</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KShisen</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KShisen</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KShisen</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KShisen</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKShisenxx</name>
  <summary>Shisen-Sho Mahjongg-like Tile Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Hra s dlaždicemi Šisen-Šo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego de fichas similar al Shisen-Sho Mahjongg</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Shisen-Sho Mahjongg-achtig stenenspel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Jogo de Peças à Mahjongg Shisen-Sho</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogo de peças parecido com Shisen-Sho Mahjongg</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Шісен-шо, схожа на маджонґ гра з плитками</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxShisen-Sho Mahjongg-like Tile Gamexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KShisen is a solitaire-like game played using the standard set of Mahjong tiles. Unlike Mahjong however, KShisen has only one layer of scrambled tiles.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KShisen es un juego de solitario que se juega usando las fichas típicas del Mahjong. Al contrario del Mahjong, KShisen solo tiene una capa de fichas barajadas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KShisen is een solitaire-achtig spel dat wordt gespeeld met de standaard set Mahjong stenen. Anders dan Mahjong heeft KShisen slechts één laag door elkaar gehaalde stenen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KShisen é um jogo solitário, jogando com um conjunto-padrão de peças do Mahjong. Ao contrário do Mahjong, contudo, o KShisen só tem uma camada de peças baralhadas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KShisen — гра, подібна до пасьянсу, у якій використовуються плитки маджонґа. Втім, на відміну від класичної гри у маджонґ, у KShisen ви матимете справу лише з одним шаром плиток.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKShisen is a solitaire-like game played using the standard set of Mahjong tiles. Unlike Mahjong however, KShisen has only one layer of scrambled tiles.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://games.kde.org/game.php?game=kshisen</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kshisen</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdegames/kshisen/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kshisen.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kshisen</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
